jobberman.com.gh 2015-12-12

# Privacy Policy-Latest Job Vacancies in Ghana

**Privacy Policy**

Created: September 21, 2009

Questions or suggestions arising from this policy should be directed to [info@jobberman.com.gh](mailto:privacy@jobberman.com) 

All information regarding a job offer is from sources deemed reliable. No representation is made as to the accuracy thereof, and such information is subject to errors, omission, and change of details without notice.   

**Jobberman’s Privacy Statement**

Jobberman is a job search and career development company operating in the online career space in Nigeria. Jobberman is very sensitive to privacy issues. Any user information we collect is considered private and we do not use, or share it except as permitted herein, without the user's permission. We use this personal information at Jobberman to provide the best quality service possible. This privacy statement applies only to information collected by web addresses in the [jobberman.com.gh](mailto:jobberman.com) domain, which is hereafter referred to collectively as Jobberman. We believe it is important you know how we treat the information you may provide to us.

**Information Collected by Jobberman:**

Jobberman collects user information from several areas of the site including the ' Membership Registration' area. Jobberman tracks the IP address of a user's computer or place a "cookie" in the browser files of a user's computer. This is required by Jobberman’s services to provide automated features. IP address and cookie log data is analyzed to better understand traffic flows and user preferences.

**Use of Information Collected:**

Collected information helps Jobberman understand its users' needs better, in order to improve its product and service offerings. Personal information may be used to contact users for the purpose of research, product development, marketing, or customer service, if the user has opted to receive such communication. Jobberman may make personal information on CVs/resumes as well as other supplied information available to recruiters on a need basis where the intended use is to make available job opportunities to users. Jobberman will not be helod liable for any alternative use of such information by any individual or organization. User search activity is collected and analyzed and may be utilized by Jobberman in the aggregate or in the abstract for a variety of business purposes.

**Use of Email Tools:**

Upon registration, you may decide to subscribe for some offerings e.g. news, promotional materials. If you no longer wish to receive our newsletters and promotional communications from Jobberman, you may opt-out of receiving them by following the instructions included in our newsletters, communication materials, or by emailing us at [info@jobberman.com.gh](mailto:email@jobberman.com).

 **Opt-Out Policy:**

We offer visitors to the Site a means for controlling the use of session information. If, at any time after registering for information or ordering our services, you change your mind about receiving information from us or about the use of information volunteered by you, please send us a request specifying your new choice to [tech.support@jobberman.com.gh.](mailto:tech.support@jobberman.com.) 

To opt out of marketing or promotional emails, please either click **'unsubscribe'** in the body of the email communication or go to [edit your Jobberman.com.gh profile](http://www.jobberman.com/applicant/profile "Edit profile link"), under **Personal** tab set **I want to receive regular job alerts in my e-mail** to **No**. 

 **Shared information:**  

Jobberman makes every possible effort to preserve user privacy; we may however need to disclose personal information when required by law or in the process of conducting our business transactions.

Jobberman does not sell, rent, or lease user information to any third party, except stated otherwise (such as is in the case of CVs). While Jobberman endeavors to ensure the highest level of standards with a similar respect for user privacy, Jobberman cannot be responsible for losses or damages that can result from a third party.

**Security of personal information:**

Jobberman takes every reasonable precaution to secure personal information within both its computers and its physical premises.

The security of your personal information is central to Jobberman. We follow global industry standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and receipt. No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however. Therefore, while we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.

If you have any questions about security on our Web site, you can email us at [info@jobberman.com.gh](mailto:privacy@jobberman.com).

**Changes to personal information:**

You may correct or update your personally identifiable information by making the change on your member account. If you no longer desire our service, you may deactivate your membership by sending an email to [info@jobberman.com.gh](mailto:contracts@jobberman.com).

**Changes to this Privacy Statement:**

If Jobberman decides to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes to this privacy statement, the homepage, and other places we deem appropriate so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it.

Jobberman reserves the right to modify this privacy statement at any time, so please review frequently. If we make material changes to this policy, we will notify you here, by email, or by means of a notice on our home page.
